{
  "questionList":{
    "question1":[
      {
        "id":1,
        "question":"The Plaka is the oldest quarter of which city?",
        "option1":"Athens",
        "option2":"Prague",
        "option3":"Rome",
        "answer":"Athens"
      },
      {
        "id":2,
        "question":"What is an axolotl?",
        "option1":" A type of mortice lock",
        "option2":"A species of salamander",
        "option3":"A nerve in the brain",
        "answer":"A species of salamander"
      },
      {
        "id":3,
        "question":"The Panama Canal was officially opened by which US president??",
        "option1":"Woodrow Wilson",
        "option2":"Herbert Hoover",
        "option3":"Calvin Coolidge",
        "answer":"Woodrow Wilson"
      },
      {
        "id":4,
        "question":"In which opera did Maria Callas make her last appearance at Covent Garden?",
        "option1":"Madame Butterfly",
        "option2":"Carmen",
        "option3":"Tosca",
        "answer":"Tosca"
      },
      {
        "id":5,
        "question":"Which US city is located on the Maumee River at Lake Erie?",
        "option1":"Detroit",
        "option2":"Toledo",
        "option3":"Cleveland",
        "answer":"Toledo"
      },
      {
        "id":6,
        "question":"Which one is smallest ocean in the world?",
        "option1":"Indian",
        "option2":"Pacific",
        "option3":"Arctic",
        "answer":"Arctic"
      },
      {
        "id":7,
        "question":"In which country White elephant is found?",
        "option1":"India",
        "option2":"Srilanka",
        "option3":"Thailand",
        "answer":"Thailand"
      },
      {
        "id":8,
        "question":"Which country is known as playground of Europe?",
        "option1":"Switzerland",
        "option2":"Italy",
        "option3":"Germany",
        "answer":"Switzerland"
      },
      {
        "id":9,
        "question":"Total number of Oceans in the world is?",
        "option1":"4",
        "option2":"5",
        "option3":"3",
        "answer":"5"
      },
      {
        "id":10,
        "question":"Which one is the biggest Island in the world?",
        "option1":"Finland",
        "option2":"Sumatara",
        "option3":"Greenland",
        "answer":"Greenland"
      },
      {
        "id":11,
        "question":"In Which ocean Bermuda Triangle region is located?",
        "option1":"Atlantic",
        "option2":"Pacific",
        "option3":"Indian",
        "answer":"Atlantic"
      },
      {
        "id":12,
        "question":"Which is the largest ocean in the world?",
        "option1":"Pacific",
        "option2":"Indian",
        "option3":"Arctic",
        "answer":"Pacific"
      },
      {
        "id":13,
        "question":"Which country first introduces bullet train?",
        "option1":"France",
        "option2":"Germany",
        "option3":"Japan",
        "answer":"Japan"
      },
      {
        "id":14,
        "question":"Lisbon is the capital of?",
        "option1":"Portugal",
        "option2":"Canada",
        "option3":"Germany",
        "answer":"Portugal"
      },
      {
        "id":15,
        "question":"Yen is the currency of which country?",
        "option1":"South Korea",
        "option2":"North Korea",
        "option3":"Japan",
        "answer":"Japan"
      },
      {
        "id":16,
        "question":"Sofia is the capital city of which country",
        "option1":"Hungary",
        "option2":"Poland",
        "option3":"Bulgaria",
        "answer":"Bulgaria"
      },
      {
        "id":17,
        "question":"International Women's day celebrated on?",
        "option1":"8th March",
        "option2":"6th Sept",
        "option3":"4th April",
        "answer":"8th March"
      },
      {
        "id":18,
        "question":"La Paz is the capital of?",
        "option1":"Bolivia",
        "option2":"Brazil",
        "option3":"Chile",
        "answer":"Bolivia"
      },
      {
        "id":19,
        "question":"Sultan Ahmed Mosque is located in?",
        "option1":"Macca",
        "option2":"Karachi",
        "option3":"Istanbul",
        "answer":"Istanbul"
      },
      {
        "id":20,
        "question":"Krone is the currency of?",
        "option1":"Finland",
        "option2":"Denmark",
        "option3":"Greece",
        "answer":"Denmark"
      },
      {
        "id":21,
        "question":"Rand is the currency of?",
        "option1":"South Africa",
        "option2":"Iran",
        "option3":"Romania",
        "answer":"South Africa"
      },
      {
        "id":22,
        "question":"Which is the largest producer of cotton?",
        "option1":"China",
        "option2":"India",
        "option3":"Nepal",
        "answer":"India"
      },
      {
        "id":23,
        "question":"Which was the first country to introduce VAT?",
        "option1":"France",
        "option2":"England",
        "option3":"USA",
        "answer":"France"
      },
      {
        "id":24,
        "question":"Vietnam war ended in the year?",
        "option1":"1975",
        "option2":"1967",
        "option3":"1962",
        "answer":"1975"
      },
      {
        "id":25,
        "question":"Capital of Norway?",
        "option1":"Bergen",
        "option2":"Oslo",
        "option3":"Stavanger",
        "answer":"Oslo"
      }
      ]
  }
}
